Subtitles by explosiveskull,
johnnydeep & HarboDomino
(suspenseful music)
How much further?
- Uncle Ammon, how far shall we go?
- Until I say we've walked enough.
Can't we just stop and rest for a bit?
(fast paced drumming)
(singing in foreign language)
This spot will do.
- What is that?
- Dig.
- Dig? Dig what?
- Dig a hole.
- I'm not here to dig for you!
- You're here because you were too curious.
- But why should I dig a hole?
- Because I say so. Take it!
(suspenseful music)
(panting)
(shovel clanking)
Done. I'm really hungry.
Then eat.
- Don't you want to join me?
- I'm not hungry.
Don't be angry, uncle. I didn't mean it.
I'm just tired and hungry.
I'm not angry, but you should
have stayed away from it.
This was not something you were supposed
to see. That's why you are here now.
Otherwise, I would have taken
this trip alone.
(low roaring)
Don't touch it.
It's just a box.
What is wrong with you?
- What happens next?
- We must bury it.
Bury it? Did we walk for
two days to bury a box?
Yes.
Why?
(thudding)
I think you've heard the stories.
Yes.
Then you know why.
Come on! They are just
spooky stories for kids.
They are true!
It will be found.
Do as you like, old fool.
Bury it if it makes you feel better.
Nobody is going to
find it out here.
It was found before and
it will be found again.
Who would look for a box here?
There's nothing but snakes and scorpions.
This box will be found.
Next time you want to teach
me a lesson, do it at home.
You didn't have to drag me here.
Wait till people hear this story.
- Nobody has to know we were here.
- Nobody will find out.
- But someone already knows.
- Who?
(gun firing)
(ominous string music)
(speaking in foreign language)
(gun firing)
(eerie orchestral music)
(gentle string music)
(laptop slamming)
(clicking)
(ringing)
God damn it.
Oh, here we go.
Hello?
[Brice] Molly, it's me.
Ah, good morning, Me.
Starting early today are we, Me?
Listen, I've been online
for the past couple of hours
looking at all the usual sites,
and we're not on any of
the top lists, not one.
And you're calling to
tell me this because?
Well who else am I gonna call?
Okay, first of all, calm down.
You're gonna give yourself an
aneurism.
Second, it's gonna be fine.
I know, I'm sorry, I...
This was supposed to be fun,
remember?
I'm sorry, I just, I need
this to be a big season or...
It will be.
I'm gonna be at the office soon,
okay?
I'm heading over there now.
You stay by the phone.
Maybe things will pick up.
I'll be in soon.
[Molly] Okay, see you soon.
All right.
(screaming)
(laughing)
(clock chiming)
(bell ringing)
[Ramona] Looking for
anything in particular?
Not really, just looking
around, thanks.
(clocks ticking)
Some amazing stuff in here.
Is it authentic?
It is, hence the price.
Holy shit.
To most, that dream catcher
would be
nothing more than a decorative
piece,
something to put out on the
patio.
But to that one person out
there, the right person,
someone plagued with
nightmares for instance,
it is nearly priceless.
I don't know if I'm
your bread and butter
type of customer, but your
shop is speaking my language.
Incredible stuff.
Have you ever heard of escape
rooms?
I run a popular one
here in town, Deranged.
Maybe you've heard of it?
It's a pretty cool deal.
You should try it some time.
Listen, I'm lookin' for
somethin' to,
to spice it up a little
bit, something special,
know what I mean?
I gotta stay a cut above the,
(low rumbling music)
above the competition.
[Ramona?] You see anything
to your liking so far?
Yeah, actually I do.
What is that?
Oh, nothing you'd be
interested in.
I'm interested, it's perfect.
It's nice and foreboding.
It is, but it's not for sale.
Are you sure?
[Ramona?] Quite sure.
What am I missing?
You uh, you sell things here,
right?
I do, and some things, I do
not sell.
This box is not to be trifled
with.
It's no toy, no simple decor
piece.
Why don't you try one of the
iron cast
candle holders over there?
I'm sure that it would do wonders
for your room's ambiance.
Nah, that box, that box has me
hooked.
It just,
It has a way of doing that.
What, it's got voodoo powers
coursing through it, huh?
Voodoo has nothing to do with
it.
That box has a history, a dark
one.
You're just reeling me in more
and more,
you know that, right?
It's called the Skull Box.
It's considered to be,
to those in the know,
one of the most cursed
objects in the world,
right up there with
the crying boy painting
and the Annabelle doll.
The one from the film?
No, the real one.
So what's the story?
No one knows where
it came from originally
or who made it.
It's reputed to hold a demon
inside of it,
a very old one.
All is well as long as
the box remains closed,
which it is, always.
A demon, huh?
You really believe in all that?
Demons are real.
It has nothing to do with
believing or disbelieving.
It simply is.
Well, fair enough, but
if it's so dangerous,
why keep it here?
Better here in safe hands,
than out there in the hands
of those who don't understand
or respect the power it
contains.
Name your price.
Not for sale.
(phone ringing)
Excuse me one moment.
Hello?
Yes, I do know.
Absolutely.
(low, suspenseful music)
All right.
Don't get it wet, and whatever
you do,
don't feed it after midnight.
Okay, call me back.
(bell ringing)
Don't say I didn't warn you.
(upbeat pop music)
(throat clearing)
Can't talk, working.
Oh, is that what we're calling
it now?
I can't write my review of the
game
until I play the game, can I?
Are you ready?
Are you sure you're
ready for me to be ready?
We gotta leave this
place in like two minutes
if we wanna get there on time.
Do we really have to go?
Yes.
You are gonna love it babe,
promise.
I doubt that.
Horror is my first love.
Don't be jealous.
I was gonna wear that shirt
tonight.
Oh, well,
guess you're just gonna
have to come and get it.
This is level six, babe.
Level six, do you know how hard
it is...
Forget it.
Shit.
(phone ringing)
Hey.
Hey, you guys left yet?
[Jeff] Not yet, leaving in a
few though.
I basically have to
drag Angie to this thing
by her ankles, so hope...
(doorbell ringing)
Hey man, just one second.
Hey, nice costume, truly
terrifying.
Smart ass.
Hey Jess, Ben's here.
[Jess] Okay, I'll be right
there.
[Jeff] What about you guys?
I'm picking up Jess as we
speak.
[Jeff] Cool, see you there.
Hey uh, tonight's the night
I'm gonna ask her to move in
with me.
You sure about this?
Yeah, I'm sure.
[Jeff] I think you're crazy
to do it, give up your domain.
Bold move, my friend.
Yeah, well, I love her.
Hey.
Ah, I gotta go.
Hi.
Uh, how long have you um,
what all did you hear?
(laughing)
Me?
What did I hear?
Nothing.
Okay, all right, good.
Go for it, tiger.
She's one of the good ones.
I know.
[Jess] Okay, I'm coming.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Have fun you two.
(smacking)
Oh, thanks.
(laughing)
- Hi.
- Hey baby.
(moaning)
You look great.
Really?
Well, you are super easy to
please.
I was thinking after this
thing,
maybe we'd go out to
dinner, just the two of us?
Really?
That's nice.
Yeah, I thought it'd
be nice to just have
a little alone time without
the Jeff and Angie show.
(laughing)
You know, just a little time to
us
just to talk, whatever.
What'd you wanna talk about?
Nothing, just...
Oh my god.
You're pregnant, aren't you?
No, no, nothin' like that.
Okay.
But I do have a wife
and two kids in Wisconsin.
I like to call 'em my little
cheese curds.
We still cool?
I'm gonna order the most
expensive thing on the menu,
but yeah, we're cool.
All right, that's fair enough.
(upbeat pop music)
(suspenseful string music)
All right, uh, Jason?
[Jeff] No.
[Ben] Okay, Michael.
What about Pennywise?
You are killing me, man.
Please, jump into this century.
This century, what
are you talking about?
Hey, I see that.
Jess, I'm just tryin'
to stop your boyfriend
from embarrassing himself
with a lame costume this year,
again.
Oh, again?
Yeah, again.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I know what you're
talking about,
and the Wheeler from Return to
Oz,
that is an all-time classic.
(laughing)
Come on, I mean, remind me
what you were again last year.
Not that it needs reminding,
but I was,
babe, why don't you remind him?
Oh, let's see.
You were, what were you?
Oh, that donkey man thing.
Incorrect.
I was Craig, the lamb mask-wearing
killer from You're Next.
Yes, of course, it's
very, very original, mm hmm.
Now did you get your
mask in the kids section
with all the other 16-year old
kids?
Ooh, funny.
The movie was rad, it's an
instant horror film classic.
[Ben] Okay, it was not and it
is not.
Can we...
Don't worry, they'll
tire themselves out.
[Jeff] Modern horror classic,
it's a different thing.
[Ben] Modern horror
classic, that's an oxymoron.
Here, go on and take one.
Pass it on to friends.
Is this kinda thing really
that popular?
Escape rooms?
You bet, yeah, they've been
growing over the last few years.
But they're really, really,
really
starting to catch fire now.
Hm.
Is it really that scary?
I'm not like the horror
aficionado that my friends are.
Not really a fan at all, to be
honest.
Oh, yeah, they're not
all horror based like ours,
but we topped the list
that year for a reason.
You're gonna have a
killer time. (chuckling)
(throat clearing) I'm sorry,
they pay me to say things like
that.
Gotcha.
That's what makes horror.
It was more than just CGI...
Your mom?
She was an instant classic.
When I met her, she was so
gorgeous.
Ooh.
(laughing)
You son of a bitch.
- Jeff?
- Yeah.
Hi, I'm Brice, nice to meet
you.
I've read some of your articles
before.
You have great taste in horror.
- Yes I do.
- Yeah?
Some of us aren't so lucky,
are we Ben?
- Hi.
- Hi there.
And you are?
- Hi, Angie.
- Angie, pleasure.
That must make you Jess.
- Yes, hi.
- Hi.
Well, welcome.
It's 8:00pm, it's your slot.
We are punctual, if nothing else
here.
Time is always at the
forefront of our minds,
as it will be with you too soon
inside.
Follow me.
[Jeff] Let's go.
[Angie] What are you guys
gettin' into?
[Jess] Here we go.
(crickets chirping)
RJ.
Dude, you're supposed to be in
the room.
The 8:00pm group is already with
Brice.
I'm going, I'm going.
And let's do the boss man a
favor
and not blaze up at work.
It helps me get into
character.
You wouldn't understand,
you're not an actor.
Oh, that makes two of us.
Next pilot season, I'm
gonna book the big one.
Bullshit.
Sorry, what was that?
I'm not paid enough for this.
Tic tac it and run.
Have fun.
[RJ] Yep.
(door banging shut)
The concept of the escape
room's fairly simple.
You have to find a way
to unlock the front door
and get out, that's it.
You have 55 minutes to do that.
The room is full of clues and
puzzles
that you have to use to escape.
Work together.
Don't overthink everything.
That being said, anything,
no matter how subtle,
could be vital in helping you to
survive.
Ooh.
(laughing)
Remember, every second counts.
Once we lock you in, you're in.
There are no phones in there, no
wireless,
so your cellphones are useless.
And it's soundproof, so our
neighbors
aren't annoyed by your screams.
(laughing)
The only way out is to follow
the clues.
You ready?
Let's do this.
Let the games begin.
(clapping)
(laughing)
Now, follow my voice to hell.
[Jess] I don't like this at
all.
[Angie] This is your idea of a
date?
[Jess] How long do we have
to keep these things on for?
(metal latch clanking)
[Jeff] Take it off guys.
[Jess] Oh my god.
(laughing)
(electric buzzing)
(low suspenseful music)
[Jeff] Yeah.
Oh yeah.
What kind of a weirdo
thinks up a place like this?
(whooshing)
(latch clanking)
How do people not love horror,
huh?
You're such a geek.
Lucky for me, you make
it up in other ways.
Mm hmm.
It's in my blood, babe.
And god willing, one day we
will get our script produced,
etch our names among
the titans of the genre.
[Ben] That's right. (laughing)
Can I get a coffee please?
[Molly] Above my pay grade.
Right.
Okay.
Come here.
(clicking)
[Richard On Recorder]
My name is Richard Doyle.
If you are listening to this,
then I am,
I am now dead.
My body will never be found.
I'm sure my son's disposed of it
by now,
like he did the others,
including his mother's.
I tried to stop him, I tried.
I saw the warning signs early
on.
Jonathan,
is not normal.
His mind is wrong, twisted.
When I look into his
eyes, I, I see nothing.
It's just emptiness.
He is in every sense of the
word, evil.
Evil. (laughing)
[Richard On Recorder]
This was his killing room,
a place of pain and suffering.
There were times I would swear
the room itself was alive,
watching me, as if it,
he isn't lost to us,
his soul has been absorbed
into the very walls themselves.
I've done my best to
lock him in here forever,
body and soul.
Whatever you do, don't let him
out.
Just get out before he
gets you, and he will.
It's only a matter of,
time.
Showtime.
(beeping)
(suspenseful string music)
Okay, so, where do we start?
Look around the room, take it
all in.
Anything could be a clue.
Mm, I'll be on Facebook if you
need me.
Uh, no wireless, remember?
Oh god, I forgot.
Hurry up.
I'm bored already.
Have no fear, I'm a
master at these things.
By the by, the tickets just
came online for the thing,
35 millimeter, we are going.
Oh hell yeah, that's the one
remake
that's better than the original.
What?
That remake sucks.
No, I'm talking about
the John Carpenter version.
You know he made a remake
of the 1954 original.
You knew there was an original,
right?
[Jeff] Yeah, of course.
Oh no, no no no no,
go stand in the corner.
You stand...
That's disappointing, you
disappoint.
You're scared of the dark.
(laughing)
All right, all right,
but let's figure out
what we gotta do, okay?
Look for patterns or
anything out of the ordinary,
positions of things.
Two chairs, upright.
Imagine that.
(laughing)
There's a bookshelf, and
there's tons of books on it.
Check it out.
Three black studs on the ship
thing.
We have this cabinet.
There's a lock on here
(smacking)
with three numbers.
Six, six, six.
(chain rattling)
What was that?
Came from the dark side.
Why don't you go check it?
(squealing) No, after
you, smart ass, you go.
Stand back, wussies,
I'll take care of this.
(eerie string music)
That's pretty good.
Think we found Jonathan.
Who's Jonathan?
- Come on.
- Really?
Jonathan, the son, the
killer of his parents.
Oh, I guess I wasn't paying
attention.
[Ben] That figures.
So what's he gonna do?
Is he just gonna, stand
there and try to spook us?
I don't know.
Doesn't talk much, does he?
This is sweet.
(low rumbling)
(voices whispering indistinctly)
(speaking in foreign language)
(sniffing)
(pulsing ominous music)
Hmm.
Anything?
No, unless we need to make
pancakes.
There's some stuff up on this
mantle.
Eraser.
Okay, I've done my part.
Thank you very much.
[Jeff] Check the jars, are
they empty?
[Ben] Yeah.
Um, we have a pattern on this
lock.
It's red, green, blue.
Red green blue, red
green blue, red green blue.
Red green blue.
(booming)
(screaming)
Papa Doyle, ladies and
gentlemen.
Nice find, Angie.
Is it just me, or did it
just get really cold in here?
Ben, your girlfriend's nippin'
out.
(glasses clanking)
Ohh yes.
The master.
Two gold coins, definitely a
clue.
(coins jangling)
All right.
Hey hey, check it out.
[Angie] And, what?
The handle's missing.
I call that a clue.
I call that poor
craftsmanship.
Hmm.
Every detail matters.
Ah, so noted master.
I love it when she calls me
that.
[Angie] I thought this place
was supposed to be scary?
I just feel like I'm back in
school
taking my SATs.
[Ben] You didn't think that
was scary?
A little bit.
I don't hear the phone
ringing.
[Molly] Because it's not.
That's not good.
People should be lined up out
the door.
Relax, the season just
started.
That's my point, it's opening
weekend.
The phone should be ringin' off
the hook.
Well, you know, we're
not the hot new kid
on the block anymore.
I mean, there's other escape
rooms popping up in town.
We can't have another
season like last year,
or that's it, it's over.
[Molly] You can't win every
year, dude.
I mean, being voted number
one once is impressive.
That was two years ago.
Who gives a shit about two years
ago?
You gotta stay relevant.
Okay.
All right, I don't really do
good with feel good talks,
so let's just get this over
with.
You are too hard on yourself.
This is just a job, it's not who
you are.
Well it sure as hell is now.
I put all my money into this.
I lost my wife over this.
Without it, who am I?
A decent guy doing the best he
can.
Decent, huh?
You really think so?
You see that box I brought in
earlier?
With the skull on it?
I bought it from the
shopkeeper
at the antique store around the
block.
She said it's one of
the most cursed objects
in the world, that there's
a demon inside of it.
Gotta drum up business somehow,
right?
Pay off the mountain of
bills I have piling up.
Do you pay attention to the
horror films that you watch,
Mister Horror King?
You don't ever mess with that
weird kinda paranormal stuff.
Ever.
What?
Never took you for the
type to believe in all that.
Hey, if the demon comes
out and attacks us all,
I will duly apologize, you have
my word.
Very funny.
(phone ringing)
Bigger the scares the
better the experience.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Thank you for calling
Deranged, this is Molly.
Oh, hey mom.
Yeah, yeah it's a little slow
around here.
Yeah, fuck off.
[Ben] How we lookin' on time?
46 minutes and counting.
We got a black safe, anyone
check this?
Silver lock.
[Jeff] Yep, we need a key.
[Ben] Round key.
[Jeff] Key, a key, a round
key.
Where would I be if I were a
key?
[Ben] Okay, round key.
Oh boys.
I think I got somethin' for ya.
- [Ben] Yeah?
- Yeah.
[Ben] So what you got?
Look, see, there's symbols in
this one
and then there's shapes in that
one.
Oh yeah, good eye, Columbo.
Ah yes.
So now what?
So now we think, we
put our heads together.
We have to figure out what
these patterns have in common
and how they can get us outta
here.
Oh, this is totally stressing
me out.
Are you trying to stress me out,
babe?
You know I turn into a
lioness when I get stressed.
I don't think you need my help
for that.
[Angie] Mm, thanks.
(buzzing)
What the hell?
(keys clacking)
(metal chain rattling)
Jesus, I forgot that guy was
in here.
(suspenseful music)
Woah.
[Ben] He's closer now.
What?
[Jess] He was against the wall
before,
or at least he was closer to it.
Ah okay, okay, I get it.
So a friend of mine told
me about a escape room
he went to about a year ago.
It was something like this,
but it was zombies or something.
Anyway, so our friend here,
let's call him Stitchface,
well he's got this chain
wrapped him around,
it's connected to the wall.
So, every five minutes or so, on
the dot,
the cog releases some chain,
it gives him more room to work
with.
(gasping) So he gets closer to
us?
Yes, and if he gets to
us before we get out...
What?
We die, or whatever, game
over.
All right everybody, stakes
are raised.
Game on, we gotta get outta
here.
(ominous music)
Okay, we got the patterns on the
painting,
triangles, gotta look for that.
We got the colors, the
colors mean somethin',
red green blue.
What?
I have no idea.
Just, anything, anything with
the colors.
Okay, don't overthink it.
Just look around.
These colors come into play
somewhere, they have to.
Okay, think.
Jess, you find anything?
Um, nothing obvious, anyway.
There's just a bunch of normal
books,
no codes written in them
or any pages missing
or anything like that.
Look at you getting into this.
I'm impressed.
Well, I know that you
wanna get out of here
more than any of us,
so I do it all for you.
That's why we're BFFs.
BFFs.
Wait.
What?
Of course.
What do you see?
Uh, books.
[Jeff] And?
Enlighten us already.
Red,
green,
blue.
- Oh.
- [Ben] Shit.
Five, three, four,
five three four.
Oh, there we go kid, yes.
(laughing)
Five, three, and four.
(lock clicking)
[Jess] Ooh.
Aha.
We have a key ladies and
gentlemen.
All right.
[Jeff] And it does not fit
this lock.
What else needs a key?
- Um, safe, the safe.
- Yes.
Safe, perfect.
Bring it over here.
(grunting)
Silver round key for a silver
round lock,
that makes sense.
Ooh, we're gonna be outta
here in half the time.
Scissors.
Um, what needs cutting?
Creeper's eyeballs.
Babe.
Look at him, he's freaking me
out.
He keeps staring.
He better not be staring at my
boobs.
I think he's looking at my boobs
you guys.
I can't say I blame the guy.
Angie, let's not heckle
the psychotic hillbilly, all
right?
He probably hasn't seen
any in a long time.
- True.
- Yeah, exactly.
I'd be the same way if I was
workin' at an escape room,
the silent emotionless killer.
Yeah, like Mikey Myers.
Eh, but you'd probably play
him in like the fifth one,
where he cries and shit.
Yeah.
He never cried, so...
Oh, yes, yes, fifth Halloween.
Girl was in the coffin, he's
lookin' over her, had the...
[Jeff] Ooh, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah yeah, my bad.
- Boys, hey.
- Hey.
Remember that thing?
Right, time.
Time, time, time, time.
Okay, scissors.
Anything that needs cutting?
Anything.
- I don't know.
- The thing?
We got 37 minutes.
All right, what are we missing?
Maybe we should look a little
deeper into the dark side.
Ladies?
Hm, bite me.
After you, please.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, we got somethin' here.
(laughing)
We found it.
(chain rattling)
(ominous music)
What is it?
[Jeff] All right.
What do we got?
(laughing)
[Jeff] Voila.
- Oh.
- A handle.
I'm the master, thank you very
much.
Thank you, thank you thank you
thank you.
(stabbing)
(groaning)
Dude.
(stabbing)
(screaming)
(thudding)
(dripping)
(whacking)
Oh my god!
Jesus Christ!
(chain rattling)
[Jess] Come on, oh my god!
(banging)
Open the fucking door.
Open the door!
(screaming)
Open the goddamn door!
Hey!
Open the goddamn door.
[Jess] What are you doing?
There's a goddamn
fucking camera around here.
Fucking open the door!
[Angie] Let us out!
- Let us out!
- Help!
Let us out, let us out, let us
out!
[Ben] Open the door!
(wailing)
What do we do?
(eerie music)
(crickets chirping)
(somber piano music)
Shit.
[Molly] Whatcha doin' out
here?
Lost the camera in the room.
What, when?
A few minutes ago.
Okay, so what do you wanna do?
I don't know.
It's never happened before.
I've been on the phone to the
company
for the past 10 minutes trying
to get 'em to troubleshoot it
but no one picks up.
Did you check the modem?
It's hardwired.
Mm.
Should you go check on it?
Is it a liability thing?
A bit of a gray area.
Okay, why don't you just go in
there
and pause the game for a
second...
- No, no no no no.
- To reset the camera.
Absolutely not.
They are in there, in the
moment.
I'm not gonna pull 'em out of it
now.
It'll ruin it.
Blowing it out of
proportion much, are we?
Blowing it out of proportion,
Molly?
One of the guys in there,
he's a horror reviewer
for Bloodlust.com.
His reviews get a lotta traffic.
Okay, so what you're saying
is,
you're like the chef that's
terrified
of what the food critic's gonna
write
about your filet mignon?
It just takes one bad review
from someone like that,
one, and we are history.
So what?
Just ride it out.
I'll fix the camera before
the next group comes in,
but we are not stopping the
game.
Okay.
I don't think that's a good
idea.
Fuck you.
(glass shattering)
Fuckin' asshole.
Fuck you.
(suspenseful music)
Angie, where's your cell phone?
Angie, hey, Angie,
where's your cell phone?
(wailing)
- Geez, Angie, Angie...
- Oh my god!
- Angie, Angie!
- We're gonna die in here!
- No, Angie.
Angie, you're not gonna die.
Just like he killed Jeff!
You're not gonna die.
Shut up, shut up and listen,
listen to me, all right?
You're gonna be fine.
We're gonna get out of here, all
right,
but I need you, I need
you to keep it together.
Look at me.
Jeff. (crying)
I know, I know, but
you gotta push that down.
You gotta push that down
and be strong for us, okay?
'Cause we need you.
We need to be strong, okay?
'Cause we're gonna get outta
here,
we're gonna be fine, all right?
Where's your cell phone?
In my, in my purse.
Okay, okay.
[Jess] What about the signal?
It's, it's, we gotta try
something.
[Jess] There's no signal...
What other idea is there?
We gotta do something.
Come on, come on.
Come on, damn it!
Don't move, okay?
Don't move, just stay here.
There's gotta be a fuckin'
signal.
Fuck me.
It's okay.
It's really not.
(groaning)
(mumbling)
(sweater ripping)
It's all right.
[Jess] You're lucky that
you didn't cut an artery.
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I'm scared, really scared.
(crying)
(chain rattling)
Oh my god.
(scissors scraping)
Get back, get back.
(eerie string music)
We have to keep playing the
game.
What?
[Ben] We have to keep playing
the game
and get out of here.
Ben, this is not a game
anymore.
What are you talking about?
No one's gonna save us.
Yes they will, they have to.
If you're gonna bet your life
on that,
because in 30 minutes he's
gonna be right on top of us.
[Jess] Oh my god, I can't
believe this is happening.
Look, we have to get
ourselves out, all right?
That is our only choice.
I can't, I can't.
My brain doesn't work like
yours.
I can't do puzzles, I can't do
it.
- [Ben] Hey, hey, hey.
- I can't do it.
We got to.
We don't have another choice.
We've lost a lotta time.
You and me, you and me, we
can get through this, okay?
Okay.
Yeah?
Okay, all right, come on, come
on.
Okay.
All right.
I don't wanna overthink it,
just,
okay, we need four coins to get
the key.
We have coins.
Yeah, we've got two coins
already.
We need two more, there's
two left somewhere.
All right, uh, they
gotta be here somewhere.
Okay, it's gotta be right in
front of us.
We've already checked
everything,
so it's gotta be somewhere
right in front of us.
[Jess] The paintings.
Oh yeah, okay.
This, this,
will it move?
[Jess] No, it won't move.
- [Ben] It's not moving?
- No.
Okay, it's gotta mean
something.
Fuck.
It's just fucking triangles, all
right?
It's the same as that
color black in the books.
We gotta figure out where it
fits
with the patterns.
I don't see any other
triangle.
We just have to step back, all
right,
just step back and look at
it simply and figure it out.
Okay, okay.
Wait a second, wait, wait,
wait.
What?
(clicking)
Oh, they're punch keys!
Okay, that's why it's
not a real painting.
There's somethin' behind it.
Just have to figure out
how to fucking open it.
(voices whispering indistinctly)
Angie.
Please, please.
Oh.
Angie.
Please.
Help me.
(eerie string music)
They're connected somehow.
These are, they're connected,
I just can't figure out how.
I love you.
I love you, Angie.
Don't let me die, please.
(raspy breathing)
(crying)
Just, hold me.
(chain rattling)
[Angie] He's alive.
- Angie!
- What are doing?
(stabbing)
(screaming)
Fuck you!
Fuck you, fuck you!
(thudding)
Oh no!
(crying)
I'm sorry, but we have to keep
going.
Don't look.
We have to keep going.
Come on, we can do this.
No.
We have to.
We gotta keep going.
Just don't look, all right?
Don't look over there, focus on
me,
focus on me, okay?
We can do this, okay?
Come on, come on.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
(whimpering)
Jess.
You got it, you got it.
I got it, okay, yeah.
These other triangles are just
pointing away from each other
or at each other.
Okay.
Punch these in, punch these in.
It's right, left,
(clicking)
left, right, right, left,
left, right, right, left.
You're fine.
(creaking)
Okay.
There's coins.
[Jess] There's coins, there's
coins.
Let's go.
All right, come on, come on.
Okay.
(coins clanking)
Do you have the other coins?
No, no I don't.
Who had the coins last?
(tapping)
(eerie string music)
[Molly] Turns out, it's
not such a gray area.
What?
The security camera.
If it's not functioning,
you're supposed to shut
everything down.
I'm not hearing you right
now, I'm not listening.
Sorry boss, if anything
goes wrong in there,
you are on the hook in a big
way.
Just go in there and tell 'em
what's up.
They'll understand.
No!
(banging)
(crying)
(low, ominous humming music)
I have an idea.
Don't look at me, no, no, look
down.
Why?
He's watching us.
I don't wanna tip him off.
We need every advantage we can
get, okay?
There's a smoke detector on the
ceiling.
I've got my lighter in my
pocket.
You told me you quit smoking.
We'll talk about that later.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, we need to spark the
lighter
and try and set off the alarm,
see if we can get some help in
here.
[Jess] Okay.
The problem is, it's
right behind him, okay?
So I need you to take the
lighter and spark it up.
Are you crazy?
Unless you wanna do what I'm
gonna do.
[Jess] What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna be the bait.
Give me the lighter.
Okay, here's what we're gonna
do.
(indistinct whispering)
(grunting)
(glass crunching)
Come on, come on, I'm right
here.
(chain rattling)
Okay, yeah, come on.
(pulsing, dramatic music)
(screaming)
Jess, hurry up.
Hurry up.
I'm trying.
[Ben] Come on!
(metal clanking)
Jess, come on, push it, push it.
I got it!
[Ben] Jess go, go!
(screaming)
(crashing)
[Jess] Are you okay?
Yeah.
(panting)
Why didn't it work?
I don't know.
We're not gonna get another
shot.
(somber string music)
I don't wanna die like this.
[Molly] You ever play hockey?
What?
They would this gripping
the stick too tight.
What are you talking about?
Gripping the stick too tight,
nevermind.
You just need to calm it down.
Shift it back into neutral for a
bit.
The tree trunk, that stays put,
but the branch leaves,
they just, they fall.
I'm losing track of
your analogies, Molly.
So am I.
Let's just keep our eye
on the eight ball here.
Sorry, I just did it again.
You are driving yourself
crazy, over nothing.
Just do the smart thing and stop
the game.
It happens.
This one glitch is not gonna
kill your entire season,
but if anything goes wrong in
there...
Oh, just wait, just wait.
I'll pull up the recorded
footage
and see what it shows.
If anything, we'll see
that everything was fine
before the feed went dead.
And if so, we'll let them finish
the game.
They're getting close to the end
anyway.
It doesn't look like
anyone's messing with it.
No, not yet, at least.
Woah, is that RJ?
- [Molly] What?
- What the hell is he doing?
Has he never seen a camera
before?
More importantly, why the
hell is he breaking character,
the dumb ass.
(eerie music)
[Molly] Dude, did he
just pull the wires out?
Yeah, I think he did.
[Molly] Why would he do that?
No idea.
(clicking)
Come on.
(banging)
(grunting)
(chain rattling)
I know that look.
Ben, talk to me.
We can't just keep sitting
here.
I'm not gonna go down that easy.
Babe.
Look, he holds the only shot
we have
of getting out of here in his
hand.
What, the coins?
No, forget about them, okay?
The bait worked last time,
it's not gonna work again.
[Ben] No, no, no bait this
time.
[Jess] What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go get them.
No.
No, don't even think about it.
Are you out of your mind?
No just look, look,
we are out of options.
We need those coins.
And I need you.
As soon as you get them,
put them in the slot,
and get the key out.
You'll need to move fast.
You mean, we'll have to move
fast.
We've lost a lot of time
already.
No, I'm not gonna let you do
this.
Just, keep a clear head, okay?
You can solve the puzzles.
They're simpler than you think,
all right?
You can do this.
No, I can't do it by myself.
You can do this, you can.
(gentle string and piano music)
I love you.
I'll be right back.
(low, ominous music)
(scissors scraping)
That's the only thing you got,
huh?
Drop the scissors.
Drop them, fight like a man.
Come on, asshole.
(glass crunching)
Okay, okay.
All right.
(thudding)
(yelling)
(stabbing)
(whacking)
(cracking)
(groaning)
(squealing)
Ben!
Ben.
Go to hell.
(stabbing)
(groaning)
Ben, Ben!
(screaming)
(chain rattling)
Get away from me!
(crying)
(coins clanking)
Why are you doing this?
You're enjoying this, aren't
you?
You sick fuck!
(coins clattering)
(chain rattling)
(eerie chiming music)
(objects rattling)
(chain rattling)
(gasping)
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please.
(toy chiming)
Please, please, please,
please, please, please, please.
(clown laughing)
(whooshing)
(yelling)
Fuck you!
(banging)
(groaning)
(chain rattling)
(suspenseful booming and strings
music)
(crying)
I'm really sorry, I didn't
wanna have to do this but,
(gasping) Help!
Help me!
(keys clanking)
(thudding)
Help, get me out of here!
(door slamming)
Molly!
What the hell?
- Call the police.
- [Molly] Police?
Call the police!
(crying)
Okay, okay, okay.
I can do this.
I can do it, I can do it,
I can do it, I can do it.
(indistinct murmuring)
(chain rattling)
(crying)
(screaming)
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
(whimpering)
More triangles?
Fuck!
Oh my god.
(banging)
(groaning)
Oh, fuck.
(screaming)
(crying)
(chain rattling)
(scraping)
Not without a fight, fucker.
(gasping)
(screaming)
(eerie, pulsing music)
(voices whispering indistinctly)
Help.
Please.
Help,
please.
Just help us now, please.
[Angie] Jess, help.
Jess.
[Jeff] Help.
(whimpering)
What are you?
Get out.
Get out!
(screaming)
(banging)
(chain rattling)
(screaming)
(eerie electronic pulsing)
(somber vocalizing and strings
music)
(guns firing)
(whooshing)
(low suspenseful string music)
(blowing)
(eerie string music)
(siren wailing)
(low suspenseful string music)
(bell ringing)
[Ramona] I see.
You are an acquaintance of...
Brice, yes.
I worked for him, but...
Yes, but.
Thank you for returning it.
I thought if I returned it,
it would make things right,
bring Brice back.
Oh it's much too late for
that, my dear.
The beast has been let out.
Yes.
You've seen it, haven't you?
Up close.
What is it?
I tried to warn him, you
understand.
There is true evil out there,
evil that is both nameless and
timeless,
here by means that we do not
understand,
whose origin we cannot
begin to conceptualize,
whose purpose, beyond death
and suffering, is unknown.
Some people can accept this,
some cannot.
Can you?
This demon never forgets a
face, and he's seen yours.
He's a patient little devil,
this one.
One day, in a week, or a month,
or 50 years from now,
he may come for you.
(booming)
Subtitles by explosiveskull,
johnnydeep & HarboDomino
♪ I wanted everything so much ♪
♪ That I lost everything I had ♪
♪ I lost everything I had ♪
♪ Nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Your time is up ♪
♪ Now everybody else has had
enough ♪
♪ Learn to let go, it's the
hardest though ♪
♪ Learn to let go, you'll
get the farthest though ♪
♪ Hold on, don't be cryin' ♪
♪ Why use so much force ♪
♪ Now I gotta let it run its
course ♪
♪ I wanted everything to go my
way ♪
♪ I was waiting for that day,
hey ♪
♪ I hope one day I learn ♪
♪ For now it's just gonna
burn, burn, burn, burn ♪
♪ Nothin' lasts forever ♪
♪ Your time is up, now
everybody else had had enough ♪
♪ Learn to let go, it's the
hardest though ♪
♪ Learn to let it go, you'll
get the farthest though ♪
♪ Hold on, don't be cryin' ♪
♪ Learn to let go, it's the
hardest though ♪
♪ Learn to let go, you'll
get the farthest though ♪
♪ Hold on, don't be cryin' ♪
♪ Learn to let go, it's the
hardest though ♪
♪ Learn to let go, you'll
get the farthest though ♪
♪ Hold on, don't be cryin' ♪
♪ Learn to let go, it's the ♪
hardest though
♪ Learn to let go, you'll
get the farthest though
♪ Hold on, don't be cryin'